<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on CompuNet, Inc.</title><link>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on CompuNet, Inc.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Route/Switch</title><link>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/routing_and_switching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/routing_and_switching/</guid><description>Good ol' route/switch &amp;ndash; this is our bread and butter 🎯, it&amp;rsquo;s how this whole CompuNet thing got its start!
From the traditional route/switch we know and love &amp;ndash; BGP, ISIS, OSPF, DMVPN, etc. etc., to more contemporary technologies like VXLAN with MP-BGP (or multicast, why not) control plane, or SRv6 networking is still, and will always be, one of our core competencies and favorite things to do!</description></item><item><title>Network Automation</title><link>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/network_automation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/network_automation/</guid><description>Network automation for us is centered entirely around free and open-source software, mostly in the Python 🐍 and Go ecosystems.
Automate your network responsibly &amp;ndash; we believe if it isn&amp;rsquo;t documented, tested, and in a pipeline, it isn&amp;rsquo;t ready for production. Our goal within the automation practice is to help clients embrace open source and do so in a responsible fashion that sets them up for success in their automation endeavors.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/security/</guid><description>We don&amp;rsquo;t take ourselves very seriously, but we do take security very seriously!
With that said, we also know there is a lot of hype and fear-mongering going on in the wold of IT security. We cut through the chaos and aim to provide down-to-earth, practical security solutions for our customers 🔐.</description></item><item><title>SDWAN</title><link>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/sdwan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/sdwan/</guid><description>SDWAN is its own category here rather than being in &amp;ldquo;route/switch&amp;rdquo; because this is a barrel of fun all on its own now!
There are about 10 trillion SDWAN offerings out there now. We know, because we&amp;rsquo;ve had to deal with a good chunk of them! When our clients are dealing with shopping for an SDWAN solution, or just managing one they already have, we bring our extensive experience to the table in any way we can.</description></item><item><title>Collaboration</title><link>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/collab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/collab/</guid><description>It turns out desk phones are still thing ☎️! They probably will be for quite a while yet, too!
We&amp;rsquo;ve got a long history of working in the collab space, not just desk phones, but also contact center, video calling, and of course, all the Teams and other integrations you could ever need!</description></item><item><title>Project Management</title><link>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/pm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://github.com/CompuNetInc/compunet_sea/services/pm/</guid><description>Project Management? Yeah, project management!
We believe PMs get a bad rap, and when done right, project management can and should be a central part of any project.
Working with our PMs is like a breath of fresh air 🌴! Never invasive, always engaged, we tailor our engagement to each customer so that we ensure every project goes off without a hitch!</description></item></channel></rss>